I'm Not Ready for Christmas is a family, tv movie,
comedy film directed by Sam Irvin.
Holly finds her world turned upside-down when she
suddenly finds herself incapable of lying.
(Don’t you hate when that happens?) It’s because of a
wish her niece made to Santa Claus.
And now, with Christmas coming up fast, she has to come to terms with her
natural penchant to want to fib while trying to do the right thing.
And that’s no lie.
Holly Nolan, played by Alicia Witt.
Drew Vincent, played by George Stults.
Rose Geller, played by Brigid Brannagh.
Santa, played by Dan Lauria.
Anna Geller, played by Mia Bagley.
Greydon DuPois, played by Maxwell Caulfield.
I'm Not Ready for Christmas is a 2015 American Christmas-themed made-for-television romantic drama film
directed by Sam Irvin and starring Alicia Witt, George Stults, Brigid Brannagh, and Dan Lauria.
Written by Hanz Wasserburger.
The film premiered on the Hallmark Channel on November 14, 2015.
The film explores themes of workaholic, santa claus,
honesty, christmas, compulsive liar.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.